Guide to the Herman Miles Somers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- ACADEMIC PAPERS, 1936-1979; Series II; 4' (11 boxes)
  - Haverford College
    - Lecture Material
      - notes, Political Science 135, Circa 1945-1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Notes, Government 250b, Circa 1946-1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Notes, exams and syllabi, Government 36, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Exams and syllabi, Political Science 34, 1947-1962 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Notes, Political Science 81, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Outline and notes, Social Science 11-12, Circa 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Notes, Political Science 34, 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Notes, Political Science 22, Circa 1948-1958 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Notes, Political Science 11, 22, Circa 1948-1961 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Notes, Political Science 11, 22, Circa 1948-1961 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - General correspondence, 1948-1962 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous syllabi and exams, 1948-1962 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Notes, Political Science 31, Circa 1948-1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Notes, Political Science 38, 1949-1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Exams, Political Science 12, 22, 1949-1961 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Exams and notes re: comprehensive exams, Circa 1949-1962 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Notes, Political Science 12, 22, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Notes, Political Science 71, 21, Circa 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Exams and syllabi, Political Science 38, 1950-1960 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Notes, Political Science 34, Circa 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Exams and syllabi, Political Science 11, 21, 22, Circa 1955-1962 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Notes re: Political Science 31, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Notes re: political campaigns, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Princeton University
    - General Papers
      - Memoranda, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Curriculum Committee: memoranda, 1963, 1972-1976, n.d (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Alumni Association: correspondence, 1964-1976 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Curriculum vitae and professional activities reports, 1964-1979 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Woodrow Wilson School Library Committee: memoranda, 1965, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Non-Degree programs: memoranda, 1966-1967, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Pension and Fringe Benefits Study Group: memoranda, notes and reference material, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Roundtable on Public Health Policies in New Jersey: correspondence, reports and releases, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Pension and Fringe Benefits Study Group: memoranda, notes and reference material, 1969-1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Conference on National Health Policy: miscellaneous notes, memoranda and reports, Circa 1970 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - University Health Services: memoranda, 1970-1979, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Research: memoranda, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Conference on Computers in Health Care: agenda, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Memoranda, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Public Management Committee: report, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Health Care Policy program: memoranda, 1972-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Colloquia on Major Public Policy Issues in Financing and Delivery of Health Care: correspondence, agenda, speech drafts and transcripts, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Dean Search Committee: memoranda, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Memoranda, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Public Management Committee: memoranda, 1973, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Faculty Steering Committee: memoranda and reports, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Faculty Alumni Forum, "The Elderly: A Forgotten Generation?": correspondence and notes, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - "Administration of Sponsored Projects": handbook, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - Memoranda re: proposed course on political analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - Faculty Committee on Public Lectures: memoranda, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Memoranda, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 63-64)
    - Course Material
      - Courses
        - Politics 202
          - Lecture notes, Circa 1950s, 1963-1969 (Box 11, Folder 65)
          - Examinations, 1963-1971 (Box 12, Folder 66)
          - Lecture notes, 1967, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 67-68)
          - Lecture notes and handouts, undated (Box 12, Folder 69)
        - Politics 307: notes, exams and syllabi, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 70)
        - Politics 521: notes and syllabi, 1964-1969, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 71)
        - Public Affairs 502: notes, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 72)
        - Public Affairs 503
          - Lecture notes, 1949-1950, 1965-1978 (Box 12, Folder 73)
          - Syllabi, 1961, 1967-1979 (Box 12, Folder 74)
          - Course evaluation, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 75)
          - Lecture notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 76)
        - Public Affairs 526: exams, syllabi and lecture notes, 1970-1979, undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Miscellany
        - General exams and related correspondence, 1950-1974 (Box 13, Folder 78)
        - Graduate exams and syllabi, 1962-1974 (Box 13, Folder 79)
        - Background notes re: organizational behavior, 1964, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 80)
        - Department of Politics: senior comprehensive exams, 1964-1975 (Box 13, Folder 81)
        - Unidentified notes, 1964, 1966, 1975-1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
        - Background notes re: executive organization, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 83)
        - Background notes re: congress and administration, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 84)
        - Background notes re: influence of interest groups, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 85)
        - Background notes re: media and public opinion, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 86)
        - Background notes and print material re: the budgetary process, 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 87)
        - Judicial synopses, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 88)
        - Background notes re: "Establishment?", Circa 1968 (Box 14, Folder 89)
        - Background notes re: accountability and public interest, Circa 1968 (Box 14, Folder 90)
        - Background notes and clippings re: bureaucracy, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 91)
        - Background notes and print material re: "Urban Policy Analysis: Health Care", 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 92)
        - Background notes re: "Quality Control in Health Care," "Grievance mechanisms" and "Quality Control and Malpractice", 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 93)
        - General exams and syllabi, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 94)
        - General exams and correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 95)
        - Background notes and clippings re: litigiousness, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 96)
        - Background notes re: technology, role and significance in health care, 1976, undated (Box 14, Folder 97)
        - Graduate exams and syllabi, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 98)
        - General exams and related correspondence, 1977-1979, undated (Box 14, Folder 99)
        - Background notes and drafts re: the role of the presidency, undated (Box 15, Folder 100)
        - Background notes and Senate bill re: federalism, undated (Box 15, Folder 101)
        - Background notes on miscellaneous books, undated (Box 15, Folder 102)
        - Background notes re: accountability, attitudes towards organization, undated (Box 15, Folder 103)
        - Background notes re: Indonesia, undated (Box 15, Folder 104)
        - Background notes re: interest groups, undated (Box 15, Folder 105)
        - Outline re: Policy Seminar, undated (Box 15, Folder 106)
        - Unidentified notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - United States Industrial College of the Armed Forces: correspondence and lecture transcript, 1951-1957 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Wisconsin, University of: grade transcripts, 1936, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 109)
- ORGANIZATION & SUBJECT FILES, 1940-1979; Series III; 7' (17 boxes)
  ORGANIZATION & SUBJECT FILES is made up of papers for forty-five organizations or subjects. The series is organized alphabetically by title. The files for each title are arranged chronologically.
  - American Arbitration Association
    - Opinion, 1960 (Box 15a, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Conference on Malpractice, 1976 (Box 15a, Folder 2)
  - American Hospital Association, Society for Hospital Planning: correspondence and agenda, 1976-1979 (Box 15a, Folder 3)
  - American Medicare
    - Report, 1977 January (Box 15a, Folder 4-5)
    - Reports, 1977 April-August (Box 15a, Folder 6)
    - Report, 1977 Sep, 1977 October-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - American Political Science Association
    - Correspondence, 1949-1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - American Risk and Insurance Association, Committee on Insurance Terminology: memoranda and reports, 1961-1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Anesthesiologists vs. United, States of America
    - Reference material, 1950-1956, 1962-1978 (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, notes, memoranda and order, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, testimony (H.M.S.) and opinion, 1978 December-1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Anglo-American Conference on Independence and Accountability in the "New" Political Economy: agenda and proceedings, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Associated Hospital Service of New York (petition against)
    - Answers and affidavits, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, background material, Ingram's and Somers' affidavits, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Exhibits, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Notice of petition, petitions and complaint, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Petitioners' affidavits, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Brookings Institution
    - Correspondence and report re: Project in Foreign Affairs Administration and Overseas Operations, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, reports and conference material, 1957-1977 (Box 18, Folder 25-27)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States: correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - College of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey
    - Memoranda and reports, 1968-1975 August (Box 18, Folder 29-32)
    - Memoranda, reports and notes, 1975 September-December (Box 19, Folder 33-34)
    - Memoranda and reports, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
    - Memoranda, reports and notes, 1977-1979, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Davis (Leonard) Institute of Health Economics, University of Pennsylvania
    - Correspondence and research proposal, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, reference material and notes, 1970-1979 (Box 19, Folder 39-40)
    - Notes and handouts, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
      See also: box 38, folder 62
  - Health Research and Educational Trust of New Jersey
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 42-43)
  - Holy Cross Hospital of Silver Spring vs. Health Services Cost Review Commission
    - Brief and opinion, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence and background material, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Depositions of Oscar B. Hunter, Jr., and Laurence J. Peterson, Jr., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Depositions of John Dennis, Albert Snoke and William Dolan, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Deposition of Milton Roemer, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1964-1975 (Box 20, Folder 49-50)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1976-1979, undated (Box 21, Folder 51-52)
  - International Business Machines Corp.
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968, 1970-1978 (Box 21, Folder 53-54)
    - Speech text re: Customer Executive Program, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - International Labor Office
    - General Papers
      - Correspondence, notes and related material, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 56)
      - Notes on interviews, 1963 March-April (Box 21, Folder 57-58)
      - Draft reports, Circa 1963 (Box 21, Folder 59)
      - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Reference Material
      - Print material, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 61-66)
      - Print material and notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Inter-University Case Program, Inc.: correspondence, memoranda and reports, 1953, 1963-1978 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Legis 50, The Center for Legislative Improvement
    - Reports, agendas and correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 69-70)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund
    - Correspondence and reports, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence, minutes and print material, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence, minutes and annotated report, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - National Academy of Public Administration: correspondence and reports, 1970-1975, undated (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Institute of, Medicine
    - General Papers
      - Correspondence, reports and ballots, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 78)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - Committee on Health Care Plans: memoranda, correspondence and reports, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 80)
    - Panel on Implications of a Categorical Catastrophic Approach to National Health Insurance: reports and correspondence, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 81)
    - National Health Care Plans Committee: summaries of congressional bills and reports, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 82)
    - Advisory Committee on Cost and Financing of Graduate Medical Education: correspondence, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - New Jersey Employment Security Council: correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - New Jersey Regional Medical Program: correspondence, minutes and reports, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - New Jersey State Department of Higher Education
    - Commission on Special Health Services
      - Correspondence, reports and executive order, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 86)
      - Correspondence, reports and state bills, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 87)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 88)
    - Special Committee on Scope and Cost of Health Professions Education: report and summary, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - New Jersey State Health Planning Council
    - Handbook, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 90)
    - Correspondence, minutes and print material, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 91)
    - Handbook, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 92)
    - Correspondence, minutes and print material, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - New York Academy of Medicine: correspondence and reports, 1963-1978 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - President's Commission on Nutritional Goals: correspondence, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Roper, Elmo: radio transcripts, 1950-1953 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Teach 'Em, Inc.: correspondence, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Travelers Insurance Co. vs. Blue Cross of Pennsylvania
    - Complaint, affidavit and memoranda, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 98)
    - Correspondence, appellee's brief and opinion, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 99)
    - Record of proceedings, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - United States Army
    - Correspondence, orders and separation papers, 1942-1946 (Box 26, Folder 101)
    - Correspondence and orders re: Strategic Bombing Survey, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - United States Army Reserve Corps: questionnaire, orders and correspondence, 1949-1957, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - United States Army War College: correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - United States Civil Service Commission: "Report of the Comptroller General of the United States", 1975 (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare
    - General Papers
      - Reports and correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 26, Folder 106)
      - Travel vouchers and personnel notices, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 107)
      - Notes and reference material re: Medicare, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 108)
      - Reports, 1965-1979 (Box 27, Folder 109)
      - Miscellaneous reports re: health maintenance organizations and national health insurance proposals, 1969-1978 (Box 27, Folder 110)
    - Advisory Council on Social Security
      - Minutes and reference material, 1963-1964, undated (Box 27, Folder 111)
      - Reports and correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 27, Folder 112)
    - Food and Drug Administration: circulars and correspondence re: Kefauver-Celler compulsory licensing bill (S. 1552, H.R. 6254), 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 113)
    - Health Insurance Benefits Advisory Council
      - Agenda, memoranda and notes, 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 114)
      - Background material, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 115)
      - Reports, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 116)
      - Reports and memoranda, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 117)
      - Actuarial reports, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 118)
      - Miscellaneous reports, newsletters and memoranda, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 119)
      - Agenda book, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 120)
      - Reference material re: national health Insurance, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 121)
      - Analyses re: national health insurance proposals, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 122)
      - Reports, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 123)
      - Reference material re: Medicare, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 124)
      - Report, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 125)
      - News releases and memoranda, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 126)
      - Memoranda, undated (Box 29, Folder 127)
    - Health Services Research Study Section: memorandum, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 128)
    - National Center for Health Statistics: reports and correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 129)
    - National Center for Social Statistics
      - Reports, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 130-131)
    - National Health Insurance Task Force: memoranda, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 132)
    - National Institutes of Health, John E. Fogerty International Center Conference on International Health Costs and Expenditures: correspondence and information sheets, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 133)
    - Public Health Service, Health Services and Mental Health Administration, National Center for Health Services Research and Development: memoranda, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 134)
    - Roundtable of the Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare: remarks and correspondence, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 135)
    - Secretary's Task Force on Medicaid and Other Related Programs
      - Notes, charts and reports, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 136)
      - Reports and correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 137)
      - Reports, 1969, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 138)
      - Report, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 139)
    - Social Security Administration
      - Reference material, 1934-1957 (Box 30, Folder 140)
      - Report, Division of the Actuary, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 141)
      - Correspondence, Office of Research and Development, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 142)
    - Task Force on Women under Social Security, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 143)
  - United States Department of Labor: correspondence and personnel forms, 1955-1963 (Box 30, Folder 144)
  - United States Department of Transportation: reports and correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 145)
  - United States Economic Stabilization Agency: personnel forms, correspondence and reports, 1951-1953 (Box 30, Folder 146)
  - United States Executive Office of the President
    - Bureau of the Budget: correspondence, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 147)
    - Council of Economic Advisors: report, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 147)
    - National Resources Planning Board: correspondence and efficiency rating, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 148)
    - National Security Resources Board: correspondence, contracts and questionnaire, 1948-1951 (Box 30, Folder 149)
    - Office of the Director for Mutual Security: personnel forms and report, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 150)
    - President's Commission on Veterans' Pensions: correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 151)
    - Task Force on Health and Social Security: reports, reference material and correspondence, 1960-1961, undated (Box 31, Folder 152)
    - Task Force on Health Legislation: reports and print material, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 153)
  - United States Information Agency: correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 154)
  - United States Naval War College: correspondence, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 155)
  - United States War Manpower Commission: correspondence re: "A Community at War", 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 156)
  - United States War Production Board: personnel forms and efficiency rating, 1942-1944 (Box 31, Folder 157)
  - World Affairs Council of Philadelphia: correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 158)
- WRITINGS, 1936-1978; Series IV; 3' (9 boxes)
  WRITINGS is organized in three sections, Biographical Material, Monographs, and Speeches and Shorter Writings. Biographical Material is arranged alphabetically. Monographs and Speeches and Shorter Writings are arranged chronologically.
  - Biographical Material
    - Bibliographies, Circa 1947-1978 (Box 31a, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum vitae and other biographical material, Circa 1943-1979 (Box 31a, Folder 2)
  - Monographs
    - Presidential Agency: Office of War Mobilization and Reconversion
      - Background material re: interagency relations, 1943 (Box 31a, Folder 3)
      - Background material re: Office of War, Mobilization and Reconversion, 1943-1949 (Box 31a, Folder 4)
      - Background material re: historiography of World War II, 1944-1951 (Box 31a, Folder 5)
      - Background material, correspondence and reviews, 1947-1968 (Box 31a, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Compensation
      - Working copy with revisions and annotations, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence and reviews, 1952-1958 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - "Trends and Current Issues in Social Insurance," with Anne R. Somers, Proceedings, 9th Annual Meeting, Industrial Relations Research Association: reprints, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - "Myth and Reality in Workmen's Compensation," Workmen's Compensation Problems 1956, U.S. Department of Labor, 1957, and Social Security Programs, Problems and Policies, 1960: reprints (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Doctors, Patients and Health Care: correspondence, grant proposal, agreement and reviews, 1958-1961, 1966, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified book chapter: correspondence and drafts by other authors, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - "Grantsmanship and Stewardship: A Public View of Federal Research Grants," with Anne R. Somers, Proceedings of the Association of Management in Public Health and American Public Health Association: draft and tear sheet, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - "Poverty and Income Maintenance for the Disabled," Poverty in America: reprint, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - "The President, the Congress and the Federal Government Service," The Federal Government Service: draft, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - "The President's Office," American Politics and Government: draft, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - "The Structure of Medical Practice in the United States," Medical Care Under Social Security: Potential and Problems: speech text, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Medicare and the Hospitals: Issues and Prospects: reviews and correspondence, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - A Program for Research in National Policy Formation, with Anne R. Somers, United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: monograph, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - "The Consumer's Interest in Planning," Planning for Health Facilities Today and Tomorrow: tear sheet, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - "Delivery of Health Care: Do We Know Where We Are Going?", Social Economics for the 1970's: reprint (Box 32, Folder 21)